Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series V. BY-LAWS
  - Sub-Series 204-2030. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2030-Star Messenger Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1922-1959 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-2031. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2031-Sioux City Lodge, Sioux City, Iowa, 1923-1947 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-2034. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2034-Western Express Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1924-1959 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-2037. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2037-District of Columbia Lodge, Alexandria, Virginia, 1952-1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-2040. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2040-Fulton Lodge, Decatur, Georgia, 1937-1959 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-2041. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2041-Louisville Expressmen Lodge, Louisville, Kentucky, 1931-1949 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-2043. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2043-Wisconsin Lodge, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1936-1952 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-2044. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2044-Danbury, Connecticut, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-2045. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2045-Cincinnati Express Lodge, Belleville, Kentucky, 1928-1958 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-2046. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2046-Rose City Lodge, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1923-1959 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-2048. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2048-Magnolia Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1923-1959 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-2052. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2052-Tri-State Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1923-1954 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-2055. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2055-Booster Lodge, Fulton, Kentucky, 1923-1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-2061. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2061-Minneapolis Railway Express Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1921-1959 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-2063. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2063-St. Johns Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1921-1951 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-2064. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2064-Messengers and Baggagemen Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1959 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-2067. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2067-Welcome Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1930-1957 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-2068. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2068-St. Paul Expressmen Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-2072. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2072-Twin City Messengers and Helpers Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1921-1959 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-2073. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2073-Cedar Valley Lodge, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 1921-1959 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-2074. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2074-Crescent Lodge, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1936-1959 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-2075. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2075-Dynamic City Expressmen Lodge, Lincoln Park, Michigan, 1942-1959 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-2082. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2082-Las Olas Lodge, Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-2086. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2086-Queen City Lodge, Meridian, Mississippi, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-2087. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2087-Express General Office Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1934-1959 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-2051. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2051-Columbus Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1922-1959 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-2088. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2088-Harmony Lodge, Jackson, Mississippi, 1940-1959 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-2095. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2095-Florence Lodge, Florence, South Carolina, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-2099. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2099-Grennsboro Lodge, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-2100. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2100-Cleveland Expressman's Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-2102. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2102-Alamo City Express Lodge, San Antonio, Texas, 1921-1959 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-2103. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2103-Inland Lodge, Spokane, Washington, 1921-1951 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-2110. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2110-Mount Diablo Express Lodge, Oakland, California, 1947-1951 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-2118. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2118-Southeastern Lodge, Washington, D.C. / Lodge No. 2118, Echo Lodge, Mamaroneck, New York, 1935-1952 (Box 26, Folder 46)
      1935-38; 1952.
  - Sub-Series 204-2121. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2121-Stall's Lodge, Charleston, South Carolina, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-2125. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2125-City Offices Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-2126. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2126-Express Division Lodge, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1942-1950 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-2128. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2128-Better Service Lodge, South Bend, Indiana, 1931-1946 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-2130. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2130-New York Lodge, New York, New York, 1943-1958 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-2132. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2132-Fidelity Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-2133. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2133-Oil City Lodge, Wichita Falls, Texas, 1946-1959 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-2134. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2134-Queen City Messengers and Helpers Lodge, Fort Thomas, Kentucky, 1949-1958 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-2135. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2135-Fort Steuben Lodge, Steubenville, Ohio, 1941-1944 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-2136. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2136-Liberty Lodge, Pawtucket, Rhode Island, 1944-1954 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 204-2139. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2139-C.F. Gallur Lodge, Pawtucket, Rhode Island, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-2144. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2144-Federated Express Lodge, Kenmore, New York, 1921-1956 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-2147. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2147-Long Island Express Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1942-1953 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 204-2148. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2148-Washington Messenger Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1948-1950 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-2150. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2150-Dixie Lodge No. 2150, Atlanta, Georgia / Lodge No. 2150, Passaic, New Jersey, 1937-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      1937; 1956.
  - Sub-Series 204-2151. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2151-Victory Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921-1955 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-2154. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2154-Hollywood Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1921-1959 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-2158. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2158-Penn Central Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1920-1954 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-2160. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2160-Capital City Lodge, Madison, Wisconsin, 1926-1959 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-2163. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2163-Patrick Henry Lodge, Richmond, Virginia, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-2165. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2165-Cherokee Lodge, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1937-1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-2167. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2167-City of Homes Lodge, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1953-1957 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-2168. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2168-Capitol City Lodge, Des Moines, Iowa, 1926-1932 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-2176. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2176-Golden Gate Express Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1926-1956 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-2179. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2179-Wehan Lodge, Saginaw, Michigan, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-2184. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2184-Sierra Express Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-2185. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2185-United Lodge, Stamford, Connecticut and Port Chester, New York, 1943-1958 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-2193. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2193-Clark Lodge, Columbus, Georgia, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-2199. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2199-Concho Valley Lodge, San Angelo, Texas, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      1953 December 14
  - Sub-Series 204-2207. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2207-Tulsa Express Lodge, Tulsa Oklahoma, 1946-1959 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-2212. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2212-Tucker Lodge, Macon, Georgia, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-2215. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2215-Fraternal Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1949-1959 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-2219. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2219-Lakeside Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1925-1959 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-2221. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2221-Monteith Lodge, Charleston, West Virginia, 1949-1959 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-2226. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2226-Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1951-1955 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-2228. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2228-W.A.Y. Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1943-1955 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-2269. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2269-Hampton Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      1952 December 16
  - Sub-Series 204-2273. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2273-Cape Fear Lodge, Wilmington, North Carolina, 1939-1944 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-2325. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2325-Progress Lodge, New York City, New York, 1946-1949 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-3001. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3001-Clipper Lodge, San Francisco, California / Magic City Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1946-1951 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-3003. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3003-Global Wings Lodge, New York, New York, 1954-1959 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-3005. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3005-Empty Folder (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-3007. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3007-Skyliner Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-3010. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3010-Inland Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-3011. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3011-Evergreen Lodge, Spokane, Washington, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-3015. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3015-Top Flight Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-3016. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3016-Pacific Air Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      Oct. 16, 1952.
  - Sub-Series 204-3044. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3044-Golden Arrow Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-3045. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3045-Mount Hood Lodge, Portland, Oregon, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-3046. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3046-Iaillimo Lodge, Des Moines, Iowa, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-3047. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3047-Independence Lodge, Washington D.C., 1957 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-3055. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3055-Atlantic Division Lodge, Cambridge Heights, New York, 1955-1959 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-3059. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 3059-A.E. Larson Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-6016. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6016-John R. White Lodge, Washington D.C., 1948-1959 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-6028. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6028-Lone Star Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-6033. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6033-Heart of America Lodge, Kansas City, Kansas, 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-6071. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6071-Progressive Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1949-1959 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-6080. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6080-J.K. Chappell Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-6087. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6087-Auxiliary Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-6091. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6091-Silver Leaf Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-6115. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6115-Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-6116. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6116-Baggage and Mail Porter Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 48)
      Jan. 23, 1954.
  - Sub-Series 204-6118. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6118-Friendship Lodge, New York, New York, 1955-1957 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-6165. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6165-Financial Secretary Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-6168. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6168-Roanoke Lodge, Roanoke, Virginia, 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-6170. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6170-Lockfied Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-6226. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6226-Eureka Lodge, Jackson, Mississippi, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-6254. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6254-Terminal Victory Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1953-1959 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-6331. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 6331-Randolph Lodge, New York City, New York, 1951-1953. (Box 27, Folder 55)
      1951-53..